<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meet the Team on Plio</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meet the Team on Plio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aishwarya Geethe</title>
      <link>/team/aishwarya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aishwarya/</guid>
      <description>Aishwarya leads Partnerships, Communications and Fundraising at Plio. She has over three years of experience with Business Development at Ernst &amp;amp; Young and Thomson Reuters. She is an engineer from Veermata Jijabai Technological Institute (VJTI), Mumbai and an incoming candidate at Johns Hopkins SAIS, Washington DC for Master of Arts (International Development), 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akshay Saxena</title>
      <link>/team/akshay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/akshay/</guid>
      <description>Akshay is the Co-Founder of Avanti Fellows and an Ashoka fellow. He was awarded the Draper Richards Kaplan Fellowship and Echoing Green Fellowship in 2012 for his work at Avanti. Akshay graduated with a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in chemical engineering from the Indian Institute of Technology Bombay and is currently on a leave of absence from the MBA program at the Harvard Business School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aman Dalmia</title>
      <link>/team/aman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aman/</guid>
      <description>Aman is a Co-Founder of Plio. He leads Data &amp;amp; AI strategy and implementation. Previously, he worked as a Research Fellow at Wadhwani AI being one of the lead researchers in projects like image-based pest detection, using cough sounds as a biomarker alone to detect COVID-19 and identifying malnutrition in neonates using smartphones videos. Aman graduated with a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Electronics and Communication engineering from the Indian Institute of Technology Guwahati.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepansh Mathur</title>
      <link>/team/deepansh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/deepansh/</guid>
      <description>Deepansh is a Co-Founder of Plio and leads the Design and Development front at Plio. He’s currently working at Fair Issac Corporation (FICO) as a Solution Integration Consultant and is contributing 80% of his efforts to Plio. He has always been passionate about using technology for social good and building solutions that are free to use and impactful. Deepansh graduated with a Bachelor’s degree in Biotechnology from the Indian Institute of Technology Guwahati.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joanna Sundaram</title>
      <link>/team/joanna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/joanna/</guid>
      <description>Joanna is responsible for directing and implementing Avanti Fellow’s research and policy initiatives, and helps with focusing the data analysis at Plio. She has six years of professional experience across India, the US, and Sub-Saharan Africa. Prior to joining Avanti Fellows, she worked at the World Bank in Washington DC. Joanna started her career as a Teach for India fellow in 2013 has worked at Sunshine Schools in New Delhi and Gray Matters Capital in Bengaluru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pritam Sukumar</title>
      <link>/team/pritam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/pritam/</guid>
      <description>Pritam is leading the technology team to build a fast and scalable technical stack at Plio. He also works as the Technical lead at Avanti and manages the technology infrastructure and roadmap. Prior to joining Avanti, Pritam has been a freelance Developer in Android and Machine Learning startups for three years. He has a Master’s degree in Computer Science and a Master’s degree in Aerospace Engineering from University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vandana Goyal</title>
      <link>/team/vandana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/vandana/</guid>
      <description>Vandana is the Executive Trustee at Avanti Fellows and leads all operations and fundraising strategy at Avanti Fellows. In addition to her work at Avanti, Vandana is a Board Member and former Chief Executive Officer of the Akanksha Foundation. Vandana has graduated from Claremont McKenna College with a degree in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
